Guide to the Emil Schwarzhaupt Foundation Papers 1945-1987
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Application for Funds and Grants
  - Highlander Folk School, Lewis W. Jones and Herbert Haberland, "The 1960 Highlander Folk School Youth Project," n. d. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Highlander Folk School, Aimee Horton, "The Highlander Folk School; Pioneer of Integration in the South," Teachers College Record 68 (December 1966); 1-10; Aimee Horton, "The Highlander Folk School; A History of the Development of Its Major Programs Related to Social Movements in the South, 1932-1961-An Abstract of a Dissertation, " Department of Education, University of Chicago, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Highlander Folk School, Aimee Horton, "An Analysis of Selected Programs for the Training of Civil Rights and Community Leaders in the South," Fisk University Project #8-291, June 1966 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Highlander Folk School, Myles Horton, "A Survey of Residential Adult Schools in the United States and Canada, " n.d. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Highlander Folk School, Reports, 1953-1967 (Box 23, Folder 5-7)
  - Highlander Folk School, "The Highlander Folk School Residential Workshops on School Desegregation with Emphasis on the 1955 Workshop," n.d. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Highlander Folk School, Johns Island workshops, transcriptions of interviews, 1953-1957 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Highlander Folk School, Reports of visits and conferences, 1958-1963, 1967, and undated (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
  - Highlander Folk School, Notes on trips, 1955-61 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Highlander Folk School, Conferences and reports, 1955-1961 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Highlander Folk School, Conversations and reports, 1955-1959 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Highlander Folk School, Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1959-1964; reports (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Highlander Folk School, Memoranda and workshop reports (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
  - Highlander Folk School, Highlander workshop Project Materials (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Highlander Folk School, Addresses of citizenship-education teachers, 1962-1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Highlander Folk School, Financial information, 1955-1965 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Highlander Folk School, Information provided by Septima Clark on Highlander (copy of South Carolina's voter registration form with Clark's comments) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Highlander Folk School, Reports and activities, 1953-1955; Rosa Parks's comments on Montgomery Bus Boycott; Statements by Bernice Robertson, 1974, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Highlander Folk School, Report on integration workshop, 1956; Alex Haley's "Fuskie's Folks," n.d. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Highlander Folk School, Aimee I. Horton, "An Analysis of Selected Programs for the Training of Civil Rights and Community Leaders in the South," Part I (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Highlander Folk School, Aimee I. Horton, "An Analysis of Selected Programs for the Training of Civil Rights and Community Leaders in the South," Part II (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Highlander Folk School, Aimee I. Horton, "An Analysis of Selected Programs for the Training of Civil Rights and Community Leaders in the South," Part III and summary (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Highlander Folk School, George F. Kearney, "Highlander Folk School Uses Practical Sociology in Facing Racial Integration," n.d. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Highlander Folk School, Promotional literature, bulletins, and form letters (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
  - Highlander Folk School, Pamphlets (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
  - Highlander Folk School, News clippings and article reprints (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
  - Howell Neighborhood House, Applications and recommendations, 1955-1956; reports, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Howell Neighborhood House, Correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Applications and recommendations, 1956-1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence, May 8, 1956-July 8, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence, July 16, 1957-December 1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Reports and speeches, ca. 1953-ca. 1960 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Correspondence with Dan Dodson about the Chelsea Report, 1959-1960; notes on report (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Dan W. Dodson, "Report on the Chelsea Community Council," January 10, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Hudson Guild, Chelsea Community Council, Pamphlets, promotional literature and news clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
  - Hull House, Chicago, Applications and recommendations, reports, 1954-1957 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Hull House, Chicago, Correspondence, December 1953-February 1955 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Hull House, Chicago, Correspondence, May 1955-May 1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Hull House, Chicago, Paul B. Johnson, The History of the Near West Side Planning Board and A Citizen Participation Project (Chicago; Hull House Association, 1960) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Hull House, Chicago, Pamphlets, newsletters, and news clipping (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Applications and recommendations, 1954, 1957, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Audit and reports, 1954, 1957; newsletters, 1953-1966 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, "A Report to the Community; A Preliminary Review of Area Problems and Possibilities," 1951; Community Appraisal Study (Chicago; Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, 1952) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Pamphlets (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Ozzie Badal, "The Factual Background of the Hyde Park-Kenwood Story; A Progress Report, 1949 to 1966," 1967; Muriel Beadle, The Hyde Park-Kenwood Urban Renewal Years; A History to Date, 1966; news clippings (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Article reprints (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Hyde Park-Kenwood Community Conference, Julia Abrahamson, A Neighborhood Finds Itself (New York; Harper & Brothers, 1959) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Immigrants Service League, Chicago, Applications and recommendations, 1954, 1956, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Immigrants Service League, Chicago, Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Immigrants Service League, Chicago, Reports and Pamphlets, 1955-1960 and undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Applications and recommendations, 1951-1957 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Applications and recommendations, 1960-1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, January-May 1961 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, June-December 1961 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Correspondence, 1964-1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Carl Tjerandsen visit to Community Service Organizations in California, October-November 1962, notes (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Progress and Community Service Organization reports, 1953, 1956, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Annual reports, 1958-1960, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 3-6)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Pamphlets; flyer from Caesar Chavez's first meeting to organize farm workers, October, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 7-9)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Saul Alinsky, "Action to Equality of Opportunity," n.d.; Saul Alinsky, "Citizen Participation and Community Organization in Planning and Urban Renewal," January 29, 1962; Saul Alinsky, "Civil Rights Housing Hearing; Commission on Civil Rights," May 5, 1959; Saul Alinsky, "Seminar on Mass Organization," August-September 1965; Nicholas Von Hoffman, "Reorganization in the Casbah," November 15, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Memoranda, speeches and positions papers of The Woodlawn Organization; revisions by Tjerandsen of incidents reported by Alinsky (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Margaret Morgan Lecompte, "Dilemmas in Inner City School Reform; The Woodlawn Experimental School Project," M.A. Thesis, University of Chicago, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, Article reprints (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Industrial Areas Foundation, News clippings (Box 31, Folder 5-10)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Applications and recommendations, 1954-1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Correspondence, 1958-1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Marjorie Gladding Kelly, "Citizen Participation and Community Development; A Report on the North Kenwood-Oakland Development Project," May 1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, "North Kenwood-Oakland Community Development Project Progress Report," July 1957 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Kenwood-Ellis Community Center, Reports, pamphlets and news clippings (Box 32, Folder 7-9)
  - Lower North Center, Chicago, Applications and recommendations, 1955-1958 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Lower North Center, Chicago, Correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Lower North Center, Chicago, "Progress Report," 1958; "Three Year Report," 1959; "Final Report for Year 1959," 1962; pamphlets (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council of Chicago, Applications and recommendations, 1956, 1961; progress reports, 1958-1961 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council of Chicago, "People and Neighborhood Renewal; The Final Report of the Metropolitan Center for Neighborhood Renewal to the Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council," March 1962 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council of Chicago, Correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council of Chicago, Pamphlets, newsletters, and news clippings (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Applications and recommendations, 1956-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Correspondence, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Correspondence, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Correspondence, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), "Handbook for State, Area, and Regional Directors of the Migrant Ministry," n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), William H. Koch Jr., "Seeds of Change; A Program of Training in Community Development and Organization Undertaken by the National Council of Churches 1957-1959; A Retrospective Report to the Emil Schwarzhaupt Foundation," December 1966 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), William H. Koch Jr., Dignity of Their Own; Helping Disadvantaged Americans Become First Class Citizens; Report of the Migrant Citizenship Education Project, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), William H. Koch Jr., Dignity of Their Own; Helping the Disadvantaged Become First Class Citizens (New York; Friendship Press, 1966) (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Pamphlets, form letters, article reprints, and minutes (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Migrant Ministry (National Council of the Churches of Christ in the USA), Newsletter, Western Harvester, 1955-1967 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Applications and recommendations, 1955-1960 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Correspondence, 1963-1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Interim and progress reports on the Lackawanna project, 1957-1960 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Field report, [Nicholas Von Hoffman], November 1956-April 1957 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Field report, [Ed Chambers], April 1957-October 1958 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Field report, [Thomas C. Murphy], 1957-1960 (Box 34, Folder 8-11)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Edward Chambers, "Black Power and Jobs; An Organization's View of the Fight," October 30, 1967; "Lackawanna First Ward Community Union Project" (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), Correspondence from Thomas C. Murphy to Msgr. John O'Grady, speeches given at a community conference in June 1958 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of Catholic Charities (Lackawanna, New York, Butte, Montana), News clippings from Butte, Montana and Lackawanna, New York, 1957-1960 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, Applications and recommendations, 1957-1958, correspondence, 1957-1961; John McDowell, Dynamics of Citizen Participation Based on Workshop on Citizen Participation held at Michigan State University, East Lansing, Michigan, September 12-21, 1957 (New York; National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, 1958) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Applications and recommendations, 1954, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Correspondence, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Correspondence, 1957-1981 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Reports, Technical Advisory Committee, 1955, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Reports, Technical Advisory Committee 1957-1967 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, "First Annual Report; Citizen Improvement Study; The National 4-H Club Foundation Submitted to the Emil Schwarzhaupt Foundation, Inc.," December 1955 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, "Report of the Second Year's Work on the Citizen Improvement Study; A Project of the National 4-H Club Foundation Submitted to the Emil Schwarzhaupt Foundation," December 1956 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Glenn C. Dildine, "Citizenship Improvement Study; Final Report of a Three Year Study (1955-1957) Conducted in Pilot Counties in Five States Representing Extension's National Regions," February 1962 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Newsletter, Citizenship Improvement Study, March-November 1957 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Guidebooks for citizenship discussion, accounts of implementation in Michigan and Connecticut, 1957-1961; account of implementation in Texas, 1961-1963 (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - National 4-H Club Foundation, Pamphlets and article reprints (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, Applications and recommendations, 1957-1963 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, Annual report, 1957; "Proposal for Education, Research, Action Projects on Labor and the Problems of Unionism," July 1963 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - National Institute of Labor Education, Joseph Mire, "Labor Education; A Study Report on Needs, Programs, and Approaches," 1956; list of current projects, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Correspondence, August 1957-April 1958 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Correspondence, May 1958-February 1968 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Overview report, May 1959; survey materials, April 1958 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - National Opinion Research Center, Robert A. Dentler, Magallen Hanna Fichter, and Carolyn Huson, The Young Volunteers; An Evaluation of Three Programs of the American Friends Service Committee (Chicago; National Opinion Research Institute, 1959) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - National Training Laboratories (National Education Association), Applications and recommendations, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - National Training Laboratories (National Education Association), Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - National Training Laboratories (National Education Association), "Report of the Second Annual National Training Laboratory in Community Leadership Training," 1961 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - National Training Laboratories (National Education Association), "Take-Home Packet of an Experimental Laboratory in Community Leadership Training," 1960 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - National Training Laboratories (National Education Association), Pamphlets and article reprints (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - New School for Social Research, Applications and recommendations, 1953-1956 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - New School for Social Research, Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - New School for Social Research, Correspondence, 1955-1968 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - New School for Social Research, Progress and interim reports, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - New School for Social Research, Pamphlets and news clippings (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - New York City Mission Society, Applications and recommendations, report, and pamphlets, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - New York City Mission Society, Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - New York University, Center for Community and Field Studies, Applications and recommendations, 1953-1954; preliminary report, October 18, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - New York University, Center for Community and Field Studies, Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - New York University, Center for Community and Field Studies, Dan W. Dodson, Final Report; October 9, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - New York University, Center for Community and Field Studies, Applications and recommendations, 1951-1952; correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - New York University, Center for Community and Field Studies, Reports and publications, 1950-1954 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Applications and recommendations, 1957-1960 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Report on March and April workshops, 1960; report on meeting of South Carolina leaders, July 1960; "Human Relations Programming in South Carolina; Consultations on Human Relations Concerns Held at the Penn Community Center," October 1, 1960; Septima Clark, working paper on Training Program for Rural Community Development Workers, 1966-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Quarterly reports, 1961-1965; "Report of the Director," 1960-1963 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, Newsletter, Penn News, 1959-1962; pamphlets (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Penn Community Services, Inc, News clippings and speeches (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Resources for Just Communities, Inc., Applications and recommendations, correspondence, 1981-1985 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Resources for Just Communities, Inc., "Executive Summary; School Discipline in a Democratic Society," Massachusetts Department of Education, n.d.; "Report of the Governor's Working Group on Learning Environments," n.d. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, Applications and recommendations, 1951-1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, "Memorandum supplementing information supplied to the Emil Schwarzhaupt Foundation," April 10, 1953; "Roosevelt College of Chicago American Studies Program, 1953-1954," n.d.; "Tenth Annual Report of the President," November 10, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, "Early Version of Roosevelt University Report," 1955 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, An Americanization Program; An Experiment in Teaching English as a Second Language, 1955; comment by Wayne A. R. Leys (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt University, American Studies Program, Pamphlets and program announcements, 1953-1957 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - South Carolina Council on Human Relations, Applications and recommendations, correspondence, ca. 1956-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Applications and recommendations, 1955-1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Correspondence, 1959-1964 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Reports, 1955-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - South Chicago Community Center, Audits, 1957-1960 (Box 40, Folder 10)